const STORE = {
    questions: [
    // 1
       {
        question:"What famous actor plays Ronon?",
        options:[
            "Jason Momoa",
            "Kit Harrington",
            "Henry Cavill",
            "Channing Tatum"
        ],
        answer:"Jason Momoa"
       },
    // 2
       {
        question:"What is the name of the people that Teyla comes from?",
        options:[
            "Earth",
            "Athosian",
            "Asgardian",
            "Satedan"
        ],
        answer:"Athosian"
       },
    // 3
       {
        question:"Who is the Primary enemy in Stargate:Atlantis?",
        options:[
            "Goul'd",
            "Replicators",
            "Genii",
            "Wraith"
        ],
        answer:"Wraith"
       },
    // 4
       {
        question:"Who was the first leader of the Atlantis expedition team upon discovery of the city?",
        options:[
            "Jack O'Niell",
            "Rodney McKay",
            "Richard Woolsey",
            "Elizabeth Weir"
        ],
        answer:"Elizabeth Weir"
       },
    // 5
       {
        question:"Whos is the first half Wraith/half Human Atlantis created?",
        options:[
            "Phil",
            "Todd",
            "Michael",
            "Kolya"
        ],
        answer:"Michael"
       },
    // 6
       {
        question:"What is the ultimate goal of the Ancients?",
        options:[
            "Ascension",
            "Seeding Planets",
            "Galaxy Domination",
            "Coalition of Planets"
        ],
        answer:"Ascension"
       },
    // 7
       {
        question:" What is the name of the discovery that Dr. Beckett helped to create to fight the Wraith?",
        options:[
            "Inoculation",
            "Hoffman Drug",
            "Ancient Gene Therapy",
            "Wraith Enzyme"
        ],
        answer:"Hoffman Drug"
       },
    // 8
       {
        question:"What is the name of the Genii Commander that led the factions first attack on Atlantis?",
        options:[
            "Cowen",
            "Ladon",
            "Sora",
            "Kolya"
        ],
        answer:"Kolya"
       },
    // 9
       {
        question:"Who is the military leader of the Atlantis Expedition?",
        options:[
            "Evan Lorne",
            "John Shephard",
            "Marshall Sumner",
            "Steven Caldwin"
        ],
        answer:"John Shephard"
       },
    // 10
       {
        question:"How did Rodney Mckay defeat the Replicators?",
        options:[
            "Forced Merge",
            "Massive EMP",
            "Military Defeat",
            "Alternate Universe Tunnel"
        ],
        answer:"Forced Merge"
       }
    ],
    score: 0,
    currentQuestion: 0
};